Can you see him?
Slender Man is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Sylvain White.
In a small town in Massachusetts, four high school girls perform a
ritual in an attempt to debunk the lore of Slender Man.
When one of the girls goes mysteriously missing, they begin to
suspect that she is, in fact, his latest victim.
Wren, played by Joey King.
Tom, played by Alex Fitzalan.
Hallie, played by Julia Goldani Telles.
Chloe, played by Jaz Sinclair.
Katie, played by Annalise Basso.
Lizzie, played by Taylor Richardson.
Slender Man is a 2018 American supernatural horror film directed by Sylvain White
and written by David Birke, based on the character of the same name.
The film stars Joey King, Julia Goldani Telles, Taylor Richardson, Jaz Sinclair,
Annalise Basso, and Alex Fitzalan with Javier Botet as the title character.
Development of the film began in May 2016, with Birke being hired to write
the script and much of the cast signing on a year later.
Filming took place in the state of Massachusetts in June and July 2017.
Released in the United States on August 10, 2018, the film was poorly received by critics and audiences
but was a box office success, grossing $51.7 million against a budget of $10 million.
For her performance, Sinclair was nominated for the Golden
Raspberry Award for Worst Supporting Actress.
The film explores themes of small town, massachusetts,
supernatural, forest, urban legend.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.